A UX/UI designer who thinks that finding a healthy work-life balance is key in the creative industry to producing the best work you can.

Educated with a BDes Hons in graphic design from the joint program between York University and Sheridan College and seven years of experience working in studio environments.

EDUCATION

2015-2018 George Brown College

Advance Diploma — Graphic Design

2011–2015 York University / Sheridan College

BA Hons — Bachelors of Psychology Double Major in Psychology and Design (YSDN)

EXPERIENCE

2016— Yu Seafood

UX/UI Designer / PR Representative

- Handled all of Yu Seafood Social Media accounts.
- Photographer / Videography Editing
- Created website: E-commerce online take-out ordering system

2011— Alison Phan Design

UX/UI Designer / Graphic Designer

- Full Branding for Le Unghie Nail & Spa
- Web Developement: E-commerce / Profiles / Porfolios
- Market Advertising: Edison Chen

2017-2018 Fit Nutrition

UX/UI Designer

- Full Branding & Logo design
- Web Developement: Marketing Website/ Case Study
- Prototyping App: Using Invision

2016-2017 **FoodPal**

UX/UI Designer

- Full Branding & Logo design
- Prototyping App: Using Invision

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects, and Lightroom at an Expert Level Experience Design, and Felix at an Intermediate Level

Web Developement

HTML, CSS, Javascript, and JQuery at an Expert Level ReactJs, WebPack, and Json at an Intermediate Level

Other Computer Knowledge

AutoCad, Invision App Design, Iconic App Builder, 3D Studio Max, Microsoft Office, and Apple Office

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

Adobe Design Achievment Awards

Two time semi-finalist

Achieved OSSD

Ontario Scholar status

REFERENCES

Day Wong

Spring Ltd.
Operations Director
647-621-5559

Johnson Chen

CDW

Operations Manager 647-288-5725